We're back in here. Okay. So I'm on my main channel right now, but I'll go over, I'll go over the whole timeline. I have, I guess I will have to defend myself. And, you know, I have to reveal some things and I didn't want to. And it's like, I just push into a corner. And when you're pushed only so far, I'll give so many chances. Who would have thought like the person most upset about that situation that it would be turned out to be her.
me okay not at him who's still posting you know he's calling her now he's
calling her a predator protector oh boy ouch ouch I know I mean to be called that
by him I don't think she really cares she's more she's more like obsessed
with me and I'll go over some of the ways that's true because I will meet
but I'm not going to obsess about someone in their hatred.
And so I'm just going to do this one time,
but let's, we can go over some stuff.
So she said, so I'll just say, you know,
I just asked kind of like a personal cease and desist,
just kind of like looking into your heart.
Wow, you have to hear her.
You really have to hear her.
It is absolutely shocking.
And I have the, let me download this one second.
So she doesn't just delete it out of embarrassment because you know what you're not letting me out so easy, right?
So why don't I just not let you out so easy? It's called one good turn deserves another
Okay, so I'm gonna download this now. I have it forever. Okay, perfect. Okay, so
Mmm, how am I gonna do this? I'm gonna just put up I'm gonna put up a screen and just you can hear
I'm gonna make her voice a little bit faster so you can hear
You can hear exactly how she's how she is treating this. Okay, and then I'll go over the whole thing
I'll go over the whole thing. Okay. I guess I can go like this. Okay, share
Okay
Perfect. Okay, and then we go shit. I'll share that and then I'll just cover my screen up
Okay, and let me speed her up a little. Okay. Well, I guess I can just go directly from a speeder up a little bit
All right, folks, good morning, good afternoon, or good evening. Whatever time it is, wherever in this world it is that you are.
Welcome once more to another live stream, audio only, of IRL News Time Live. I'm your hostess, Alexandra, and aside from a little
compilation video that I posted earlier today,
revolving around a live stream and live panel that involves some cooking, I have not been paying attention to the internet today.
But someone who cares about me has been.
And it's actually unbelievable to me as to what did happen on the internet today, in regards to two criminals who I have explicitly told not to communicate with me or contact me directly further anymore.
Neither criminal embodies a sense of boundaries. I believe them both to be sociopaths possibly psychopaths
I'm referring to the sign of Judy and Delos baits. Okay, and that's public figure John Bates
Okay, are they public figures?
aka Karen aka grateful 2026 a a Dana aka peak cartel
both parties
Have attempted to contact me though. I've told them not to
I am literally just now catching up with what transpired,
I would assume on Bates live panel earlier.
And it's unbelievable to me,
from what I'm being told, though I am going to look into-
Being told how I watch it, lady, you stupid.
In regards to what it sounds like was misrepresented.
Being told, okay.
It sounds like I'm being scapegoated.
Oh, you are.
With the Brandon Kingtana situation.
Not surprising when I really, when I really sit and think about it because you are in the nature of both Karen and John Bates, kind of expected.
And it's something that I already kind of prepared my mind for.
But I want all of you to read and I'll read it out loud to you.
a telegram message that I received from Bates.
I thought I'd blocked him everywhere.
So I promptly blocked him after he sent this to me,
but I want all of you to really listen to
the level of entitlement within this school.
I want you to listen to the nurse.
I want you to listen to him actually believing
that he's in a position to make any demands of me.
Oh, watch out, lady.
watch out. I've already made it known that he probably needs to contact Riviera Center Management
and Riviera Center Properties legal team, you know, his parents' companies.
Oh, what's that?
In that way, they can examine everything in totality.
Shit.
Oh my gosh, I would love to see your porno videos.
Because I'm clean as a whistle.
Oh, you are, yes, you are.
But he's not, he's an active drug addict,
an active extortionist, blackmailer, slanderer,
bully,
overall criminal.
Okay, okay.
Someone who maliciously harasses and stalks women
after they told him to leave them alone.
I mean, it's ridiculous.
Oh, it is ridiculous, isn't it?
Come on. So let's go ahead and take a look at this. I want all of you to see this.
This is just from a few moments ago. Giving you an opportunity to remove the videos doxing my
family before this goes any further. I didn't set you up. You yourself injected yourself into
the situation with Brandon, then brought me into it further by staging his redemption tour.
We all make mistakes. You know in your heart that you're going too far.
I know you and your family were doxxed years ago.
You didn't like that, I'm sure.
So how do you think I feel?
Have empathy and end the cycle.
And then he posed, and I can't believe the nerve
of this part, he posed a Christian Bible verse
whereas he actively, publicly aligns himself.
with historically demonic entities.
Oh really, okay.
And non-Christian paths of faith.
He cites Matthew 712, so in everything,
due to others what you would have them do to you.
For this sums up the law and the prophets.
He should take that Bible verse advice himself.
No, oh, you should, lady, no, you should.
Let me give you all my commentary along with it,
because it's unbelievable.
You should.
Giving you an opportunity to remove the videos
doxing my family before this goes any further.
No!
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
Even after the days that I am no longer breathing, any material that I have put out in regards to the son of Judy and Delos Bates will remain online.
No, it will not.
Possibly other sources offline.
Because you know what?
I didn't set you up.
You yourself injected yourself into the situation with Brandon, then brought me into it further
by staging his redemption tour.
Yes.
No.
Yes, yes, yes.
That is a lot.
No, you're not.
You're lying.
Yes, you are.
I already chronicled the situation in regards to Brandon when there was an incident revolving
around a woman who truth be told is no better known as vegan patriot.
the only reason that I even thought that there could be a smidgen of a chance that Brandon had shifted
and changed and wanted to be better was specifically because of John Bates and his begging and pleading with me
to give him a chance in the moment that Brandon split that switch on me due to Sandman that came to a close.
Ironically, Brandon seems to be a bit smarter than John Bates.
He knows better than to attempt to contact me directly or communicate with me.
I just want to ask you one thing.
He does?
But, Brandon wasn't raised in what I can only assume to be a piss-poor environment as John
Bates was.
I get to learn about Judy and Daileau's bates to see that.
They thought money could fix things instead of actually disciplining their son.
Let's continue. We all make mistakes. Yes, we let's get into it. No Brandon yesterday. He posted
Oh, look at that. Look who's in this predator protectors chat
Meaning he's calling Alex the predator protector. The only predator she was protecting was I guess him, you know, but
That's what he's saying. So he and he tagged her in it. So is that contacting her, but he's much smarter than I am, right?
Sound like I'm it's not like I never attacked. I mean jeez. I never did attack or watch this
You do but here's the thing I take accountability for and acknowledge my mistakes
Whereas beats does not he attempts to cover up his mistakes
Oh, like by deleting all my videos every three months
Here I also want to make it clear that well before I decided to delve into Judy and oh my god
discussing slanderous and false things in regards to me and elements of my personal life.
All of it was unprompted. It's all been him attempting to bully and pressure me into communicating with him.
He has zero sense of boundaries. He does not understand the word no.
When I say that he is a spiritual and psychological rapist, I am not playing around. That is what he is.
Wow is a spiritual and psychological
Rapist Wow as are several others and that's not standard
That's not the only actually contact as well, but let's continue you know in your heart that you're going too far
So now he's going to assume that he knows what's in my heart. No. Oh, oh, oh
You do not know what's in my heart my mind my soul nothing
No one knows that but me well obviously there's nothing in there God it's a bunch of dust
I know you and your family were docks years ago. Yes. He does know and he's utilized as much of that information as possible
What information what information what if I use and harm me what is one thing I've used out of your docks one thing
You didn't like that. I'm sure no I didn't but it wasn't like it bitch. Have some empathy. No, she doesn't she doesn't have any empathy
No, so how do you think I feel? I don't care how you feel wow
This is just that's been out the door. This is a long time ago
Now if you cannot acknowledge my boundaries
It's time to go ahead. Well, you can't acknowledge my boundaries and I think you better get your
That's why you lost in court to everything you ever sued not in regards to the type of evil and the type of criminal that you are
John Bates
So that's all but let me go ahead and read my official statement in regards to this
Because I'm not the only one who's had to contend with this monster isn't this who else I will be well who else oh
Let me just read you the names who else oh it says a few moments ago
Though I've clearly and firmly
Told to cease all direct con communication contact with me. Well, see I did a cease and this is too, but I never said
All I said was cease using my full name.
Oh my gosh, you're doing it again.
So now you've broken the thing too, okay?
Let's see.
And then you do my parents' names.
Let's see, known as Psyche, breached my boundaries
and is attempting to intimidate and bully me
into compliance with his demand.
Guys, did any of that sound like bullying or intimidation?
I was giving her a chance.
You know why?
Because I'll tell you why.
Because I'm privacy striking the fuck out of her
I'm giving her opportunity to take those down before I finally go through with it,
which I already have now due to this, okay? So too late for you now, Alex, okay?
I will not be complying with anything Bates requests that he can attempt to
who will paint all the false narratives he likes and he will all he will strictly fail,
whatever. In addition, Bates aka Psyche is attempting to utilize Christian religious scripture
Bates turned away from Christianity permanently
many years ago in his youth.
No, that's not even true.
I mean, I said I was in a youth group
and stuff like that in my teens,
I like, you know, experiment with a lot of different stuff.
But I think Christianity is just as viable
a religion as any other.
And I think many things are beautiful.
And I do read the Bible sometimes.
I think it's a powerful book.
I do love the message of Jesus.
And so, I mean, you don't pick that up on that.
You know, who doesn't really appreciate the message
of Jesus, well, you, who would have called him
like, you know, terrible names.
Anti-Semitic names maybe right like didn't like you said good times beat it
I should be thrown in an oven because we're Jewish. You remember that you remember that Alex. Oh, you don't you do?
Oh, yeah, well your that live is probably still up, but no
It's like, you know, this is just like, you know, I think she needs as big as a as a big as a warning label as maybe like
You know him. I mean, it's like as a dangerous people, you know, it's like this is a dangerous person
It's like and you know what? It's like she's gone so far beyond anything and
And she used me. Okay, so let me just go over the timeline. I'll take this. I'll take my bag. I'll take this down. Hold on
Okay, I'll put this up. I did trust her and that's a very unfortunate thing
Okay
So let me just say
Okay, so I guess that first time that bq. I'm just gonna call him bq and I'm gonna call her a.m
Okay, just for so I'm not accused of like, you know harassing them
So anyway, so the first time bq was on the show and there's like a little controversy
She did it alive and she said is big is like psyche
Having you know predators on the show. I never watched that episode of it
I mean, I didn't because I was already live again and then before I knew it. She had come into the chat
I mean, there's a video of this and I can I have all these videos. I mean, I have to go and dig this up. Okay, but she she came on to
Okay, anyway, okay. Well, let me put up something else. So then they so here's what she's mad
Okay, well, no, I'll go over the situation like I was okay, so
She came over to my show and we had a talk and we had just reconciled at this time
Probably very very shortly before we reckon so we had reconciled and then this happened, right and she came in we had a conversation
And then after that conversation, she posted a video,
I have decided to give Brandon Hew a second chance.
That's what she said on her video, right?
And that was it, right?
I was ready for him to go off into the sunset,
not really have to belabor this, but she,
you know, she on her own side is she's like,
she's decided she was going to be, you know, on his side,
right?
I get a message,
Alexandra's calling for you on her show.
She wants you and Brandon Q on the show.
And so I don't know why I was necessary there,
but you know, she wanted me there.
Maybe so she could blame all this on me later, whatever,
but she wanted me there.
And she interviewed Brandon.
I talked, he talked, I talked about how there's a lot of false narratives, I said it looked
like it was, some of this stuff had been overblown or edited and stuff like that, that I had
seen at that point.
I had just seen a few clips, right?
And so that was that.
Then, all of a sudden.
She, Brandon's her intern, she said Brandon's so attractive.
He's a very attractive man.
He's so smart, he's so funny.
Like look at his, look at his, his streams
when he's video gaming, he has that dark sense of humor.
So funny.
She had his, I'm talking about Mortal Kombat.
There's a, you know, the streamer,
she did with the couple of hours stream just interviewing him
about Mortal Kombat and his enemies and stuff.
She like turned against Gamble.
She turned against, I mean, but she didn't really like
face as much scandal as I did over this situation.
Surprisingly, but you know she didn't but she had no she had no it's really big scandal right like I did and then
You know of course then I annex who she had been enemies with then then she spends I annex again
Then we were all the three bosom buddy or the four bosom buddies, right?
It's like we were we were all like friends, you know all friends with each other
But the thing is I was I at that point
I was maybe talking to her maybe once or twice a week
Um, and then I was talking and then you know I talked to I next sometimes
But I never talked to Brandon private privately
I'm not sure if she did, I guess she did because I don't know much of it, like some discussion or something, but I don't know 100%.
But I know Aya next had talked to Brenna and she shared her messages today with what he said and where he's like, fuck Alex and you know, and I had noticed some of these things.
You know, there's all these little signs, like when he would like kind of like, I don't care if Alex doesn't like me, like during the time when she was her friend and stuff, I was like, oh, wow.
Then, whenever the shit hit the fan, Christine Backstabbed, of course, Christine the Backstabber.
Christine is over, I mean, I have this thing, I mean, they all were making, she was making
her dinner, her rice and stuff, and then Christine, well, we got to take out for the
women in the community.
And then they had, you know, Kristaline.
Oh, I get her.
Okay, yeah.
Like, it's this picture right here, if you ever, you ever seen witches of Eastwick or
something, it kind of reminds me of that, except there's four witches, but yeah, here's
here's the uh and this is just this is all satire parody you know this was not a real image but
here we go this was their dinner they were all at a dinner together um and then afterwards they
did a witch's Sabbath and that was this picture okay so we got that well and I mean I mean yeah
we already know they're all very witchy I mean it's like you know they all talk about
You know, we're carefully you do Bible study with first of all. I mean good Lord. I mean the actual witch of Eastwick
Okay, but anyway, we can take that down. Okay. Okay. So now let's get into
Well, let's see. So that was it. But then I guess a few days later
She had a show it was about
the
the what's his name Carl's Carl and Mimi situation and then she had salmon on and this is what started all she had salmon on
And I have no problem with her talking to Samman or anybody.
She can have anybody on her show as she wants.
It's her show, right?
And then Brandon tried to come on.
He wanted to fight with Samman or something.
But she kept them separate.
And as soon as she took Samman off the show, he got mad.
And he's like, fuck her, fuck her, fuck her.
The next thing I know, I see a video.
And it says, I annex his voicemail.
It says, Bita never tried to kill me.
Did Psyche set me up?
So I went in and I was like I was like no I didn't see you up
I think that Brandon's fucking with you or something and I got hidden from the chat immediately
So so I only I wasn't even able to work with it Marcy. Hi. What's up?
You played the beginning of the video that fucking yelling is fucking unhinged. Yeah, that's giving Noah's while isn't it scary?
I know
I know I know and my father passed away and she knows that and she's pretending she doesn't know
She's also using like, you know, it's another name for my father now
Cuz I think I don't and then and my mother, you know, it's like, but you know what she's told me
She doesn't care much for well, she told me in so many words or demonstrated to me. She didn't really care for
I won't even make it, I won't even make the accusation.
I don't want to say it because it's like, it's just too much.
But I will share, here's a tweet she made,
and it's not recently, it was maybe several years ago.
The date doesn't matter, the tweet.
The point of the tweet is her sentiment, okay?
So let's just look at the sentiment of the tweet.
Not the date of it, and I never presented it
as it was brand new or specifically to do with me.
This may have been a few years ago,
but this demonstrates a pattern.
But let's look at this.
There we go.
Alexander Mayers, okay?
So that's her, right?
Tonight, I will specifically stay to every individual
who has ever gone after me and my family.
I will end your existence.
Okay, Alexandra.
So if you're allowed to feel that way,
shouldn't anybody be allowed to feel that way
that has their family messed?
Oh, oh, you're messing with my family.
Okay, hold on one second.
And then, funny how time rounds justice out, isn't it?
Right, okay, and then let's go to the next one. Here's the interesting one for a few years my quote-unquote adversaries
hi, Jay
Assumed that I'd never be a part of the manifestation of their absolute
Fears in regards to their quote-unquote loved ones and themselves more importantly because that's who will be blamed
Being held accountable to the worst of the worst
Yeah, I'm just I'm desing my shoulders off
problem is is that
What she's doing is is that illegal and slander than she's accusing me of doing it like I'm like let me get the list of
Accusations that she's made of me and this is just in one show. I can I have I have like lists of all the all the
All the slander and actionable all the stuff she said about me. So let me just read this first. Okay, so
Okay, so
She has...
besides doxing the family, right?
She has called me criminal, exploitative, greedy,
abusive liar.
Let me think about spiritual rapist, spiritual trafficker,
abuser, blackmailer, extorter, head of a drug ring,
drug addict, dirty, a piece of trash.
I mean, my apartment's a drug den.
Then about my family, I received preferential treatment.
I'm incapable of employment.
Then why do you tell me to get a job if I'm incapable of employment?
I'm wondering about that.
Suggestions property damage has occurred because of me.
Um, I would say more, more beta, but yeah, I should have lowered the volume
when Peter was screaming, many of the peer re accusations or insinuations
rather than clearly identified opinion, which is what it is.
And then it goes after all these other things.
And then it says, um, but there's a broader, here's the, here's her pattern.
Identifying family members, identifying employers.
or businesses discussing private living arrangements,
publishing identifying information,
encouraging investigators to investigate,
making criminal accusations,
making moral accusations attempt to connect online disputes
to real life consequences.
Okay, and so, this may fall under, seriously, defamation, putting me in a false light, harassment,
cyber stalking, doxing, related laws, intentional interference with prospective economic advantage
or business relationships, and intentional infliction of emotional distress.
Okay, and is there any evidence, is there any evidence to any of that, she said?
Yeah, spiritual rapist, yes.
I am a and also and you know, she's just she said poor beta poor Sam man
Poor RG. They've all been victimized by me, right?
Not like they haven't they haven't fucking been harassing me and like and saying every horrible thing they can for for a long time, right?
But I I I stick up for myself and that's you know, I'm harassing them. Okay. Well, okay
Okay, how about when you said you wanted to like castrate Samman on his when he was on a show when you said you wanted to castrate him, right?
Yeah, half the things I she listed are part-time jobs. Yeah, I
Mean and now she's both
Marcy's now she's gone as far as like, you know that there's a gas. There's that that little um
Like the liquor store I go to right I went in one day. I was on my camera. I had my I was filming I bought like a $2 cigar
and then I've used my card to pay.
And the lady said, I love you too.
I love you too, Massel.
And then the lady's like, okay, it went through.
Okay, have a good day.
And I was like, are you sure?
Cause I heard it beep and I thought maybe,
cause we can go over some of her,
because she's not going to stop.
I mean, it's like, then I have to go.
I mean, I gave her an opportunity to end it, okay?
To be the better to be the bigger person see I've been the bigger person because I do have her father's name
I do have her father's name and a lot of information about his relationship and stuff
And I have also stuff that she's told me but see I don't use those things like she does you know
I don't I don't look I don't take I don't become friends with somebody to gather information on them to try to use against them later
That's why I had I had a trust towards her. Okay. She's she she knew you know, she's not trustworthy. So, you know, obviously
You know, I don't know but I trusted her and that was stupid of me and again again. I'm stupid stupid stupid, right?
But yeah, I have I have all her family. I have her. I know her. I know every I know everything
Okay, hers is all out. I mean hers and that's why it's like I mean she should know better
That's what I think it's like because and if she doesn't know you don't know it's in my heart
Well, it's not light it's darkness and sludge and hate. I mean, that's what I mean
Yes, I do know it's in your heart and it's not good. I mean to clear that out sweetie or woman
I mean, I don't even know. Sorry. I don't want to be like, I don't use of all kinds of things, right? I mean, geez
I mean that tweet I just showed you
That's that's just one. Okay?
And that's her. I mean, it's not made up. It's not she tried to make it do. Oh, he's it's not what she's like
Look, this is not what I posted recently. Yes, we know you didn't post it recently
It may be posted maybe five years ago. Is the sentiment match exactly how you how your pattern seems to be?
Yes, okay
Yeah, you see I bless her heart. I mean bless it. I mean it needs an exorcist
It needs something because if you watch the other night she was calling out to the devil
She was drinking a huge bottle of liquor or a cup of liquor
It was like a big drinking glass full of peach schnapps or something like that
Her eyes are rolling back in her head or disappearing just turning pure white. I'm not sure she was calling on
Yeah, she was she was like and then you know shaking and she was crying. I'm apologizing to beta. I'm so sorry beta
I'm so sorry
I mean, she, I guess she needed friends.
If your friends was Christine and Bita, I mean, great.
Good for you.
I know you always want to be friends with Christine.
She was always after Christine's friendship.
And I was like, maybe that's what she was kind of trying
to do, trying to like be friends with me.
So then she could, you know, drop me and then go hate bomb
with Christine and Bita and Crystal Anne,
which I guess she wanted to do all along.
And that was, was that the point of it?
Because I'll tell you, one of the first conversations
we had on the phone, she asked me if I would consider
Being the father of her child
Okay, how about that?
Yes
Exactly. Yes. Yes, and I'm I see I'm not even repeating those and that story is disgusting
And I mean, did you join me didn't like listen, I know too much. I know too much
Yeah, she asked me yeah, she asked me to be the father of her child or potential. She said she had a few in the running
I don't know good times and maybe Brandon at this point. I don't know
But yeah, she had a few
No, that was before, that was last year.
This was because we had a three month falling out
and then we reconciled.
And this was during the reconciliation period.
This was like April to April, May, June,
like another three months.
Yes, right.
I don't know, I'm not a doctor, and I'm not gonna say that,
but yeah, but maybe she, I mean, I'll say it,
like, you know, she's gone in and out of interest
for having this, but then she was so glib about it.
One night it was like, who wants to be the father
of my child?
And Alex McQueen was like, me, me, me.
Alex McQueen was like, I want to,
and she said something like, oh, you can have,
oh, we'll have a daughter, and he can marry Alex.
I was like, I don't think I'm interested in that scenario,
but anyway, anyway, well, thank God,
like a few days later, she had gone on live
and she said she had picked the father and it wasn't me, okay?
Okay, the bullet dodged there, okay?
But I mean, I was, yeah, I was about to be, you know,
put in an Uber to the sperm clinic.
Imagine that, imagine if she was running around
with my kid, oh my God.
But that would be the real nightmare, okay?
That would be the real nightmare.
He's got a bad case of endodontics,
but I'm not sure what that is.
Listen, listen.
I can't say that I hated her.
And it's like, wow, it's hard for me to hate somebody.
The way she's going and acting right now,
and just how stupid she's being,
that
I know, I know, I know, a lot of people did try to warn me.
I know, see, the thing about it is I need like somebody,
like I really, really know trust,
come to me privately and have a conversation,
which nobody ever did.
Like nobody ever did.
I mean, I did have some like different people
with their perspectives and stuff like that,
but I didn't have anybody with a smoking gun on that.
And that's for, I mean, I don't know,
she has a lot of enemies and, you know, but anyway,
Yeah, and then God, he was like, oh, just give her back all the donations. Well, that won't do anything
What she's not gonna do anything. It won't change anything, but she's like, oh, yeah, you should do that
Yeah, whatever. It's like, you know what donations gifts
They're supposed to be made in love and stuff and I'll just take it
I take them in at the time in the spirit of love where she sent me flowers. She sent me
Groceries she and she said I so she thinks I sold the groceries for drug money now
Like I sold you think I can just go out on the street with like frozen food and what do I like what what?
What the fuck have you I've never even heard it. It's such a stupid allegation in my life
I sold the groceries for drug addicts. You didn't see me eating. Yeah, like I don't really eat all my food on camera
First of all, yeah, it's a little bit of a hard sale. I mean geez
I mean along with them. I mean all these I mean just so many
Ridiculous, I mean it's like it's so the good thing about it is that it's so crazy. I should yeah
Yeah, I should, then I'll be, pass some frozen please please for a blunt. Yeah, I know. Yeah, exactly. What am I doing?
I mean, some chicken patties and some, you know, a couple apples and a banana and stuff like that. Exactly.
Thank you very much on Trackable. My hair is pretty long now. Yeah, but and then she's also like, you know, she went, she also, when she was on my show,
And well, I mean, I probably should play some of it.
I mean, I'm not gonna play too much of it at a time,
but I will show you when she came on to my show
the first time after we reconciled,
we had talked earlier in the evening,
and she was already a little bit drunk
because she likes to drink a few times a week, I guess.
But I will show you some of this and what she says to me
and where she says,
I survived her testing or whatever and it was just a test and, you know, and she knows I'm not I'm really not a bad person and all this kind of stuff.
And she said she was sorry too. We can play all that because then we'll see who the flip flopper in the situation is. Okay.
It's turning on me for no reason. Never let me explain. I said, I said, what did I do? She texted me back. She said, you know what you did.
That was, that was all.
You know what you did yourself this you're evil you're blah blah blah, okay, so but I just do it
I just want to show you a little bit of when she first came on the show and
I was a little bit sleepy that day, but um
It was interesting still she came on and and then you can see her conversation with RG
And if I really want to get into it, you know
Are you are after the after the show she went on?
She was continued backstage with RG and Q and it got even nastier, but I'm not gonna put her through all that. Let me see
hmm
Okay, let me just take a deep breath. Okay, fine this one
Okay, here it is
So I will just get to the good good stuff. Okay, I won't keep I won't belabor you on this
I will I will keep it short and just show the important parts. Okay, let me see
Here we go. Okay. Here we go
Though
Not so beautiful at this moment, I probably look really fucked up be honest with you
Well, you want me to leave the video by the way?
I look like I just rolled out of bed, don't I?
Yeah, but you're a guy.
It's different.
You look like Jesus Christ meets a modern day,
I don't know, Jared Leto rock star kind of vibe.
It works for you.
Thank you. Yeah, my hair is pretty much, I think it's the most it's ever been. It's like, I haven't cut it since it's probably been cut.
It's not, it's not that long, really, because you have the little curly cues and what not, don't you?
Yeah, I wish it like came out like this beautifully straight. Maybe I can do that.
Um, I want your help with the selfish matter, okay? That is now, right?
I'll let you know privately
Okay, maybe publicly what it is
My loneliness is killing me because it is
I didn't realize that till today
But it is
And that's why I'm so grumpy
Oh my, oh my.
Yeah, I'm pretty grumpy too, you know.
I've been alone like a lot of my life,
like just like, you know, on my own,
like, you know, kind of even like with everybody,
or even with people around, kind of like alone, you know,
like I'm alone.
Oh yeah.
A little bit.
Never less lonely than me, I would say.
I have these cats, and so the cats, like, you know, three cats.
Well, did tricks, what happened with tricks?
Tell me the tricks update, because I'm not worried about that.
My followers know that.
Yeah, well, the tricks.
Is tricks back? Like, where's tricks?
Trace has not come back, and I have a notice in the next door with a really good photo of him.
He has a distinctive little freckling on his nose and stuff, which is like, we'll make it easy to identify.
Well, he's a great striped cat, right?
He's white, and he has a picture of him.
This is his picture. Yeah, put a picture.
Because, yeah, I think you're thinking of his mom, like Lola, and she's the gray, and then Tricks is right here.
That's not the best picture of me, but here.
So okay, so why in gray?
You got the tabby face. He has a little freckled nose. So what why are we on this channel?
Why are we not on the regular channel?
What's happening? I felt I told you I would I retract whatever I need to
You know, I don't think it has to do with that. It has to do with
There's this community striking system like the community thought the community, but it's a community guidelines or something like that
And as part of that is copyright music and I fell asleep last night that I smoked like this big vape and like
I took a big hit of it. That was like I'm gonna drive myself. I have it on my plane music
Well, I've already informed YouTube that I retract whatever I've done
So that is
Not an issue. Yeah. Oh, thank you
She's stricken. I mean, I just like I don't think any things that that I've done actually happen in issue to be honest with you
but um
What are you gonna do psyche?
John I'm gonna keep calling you John. You're gonna hate me for it, but that's who you are to me at this point
You're mr. John and I like calling you John because you look like a John
And hey, I mean, I've been a prostitute, sex worker, legal, legal, legal, legal, legal.
So maybe you're my, you know, eternal John forever, even though I've never been sexual
with you.
We are strictly platonic friends.
Oh, you gotta throw up Lenore.
Okay, Lenore, my spirit animal, I suppose.
Defending you from my sexual
Realize that over the past few years
Yeah, let me let me put you on my
uh channel cult of psyche why why are you tracking me into your cult which i'm not necessarily
opposed to what's going on with your ass well it's like uh she was she was a poor star
but i always consider the cult of two and like you know that that was
Well, I did like it, but it's
Nightmares, that's what you're calling it the nightmares. Really? I'm looking at it right now
nightmares on Elm Street
Really, really really really maybe on the lane of street. Oh, she just docks me. Okay
Look, I'm gonna be the real asshole in your life
You know you want to be lgbtq. Okay. Well, let's let it be I'm gonna be the asshole that exists in that world
You know, I'm not really well no matter what I'm born into that world
That's what that's what pissed me out about your friend goes really didn't did you hear my own?
rent about that
Yeah, I enjoyed it, like I listened to that, I listened to two episodes, kind of like the rant, but it wasn't really a rant, it was really good coverage of like, you know, probably one of like the first like debate, like real debates almost like.
I didn't get to talk that day, I got upset about that.
Yeah.
He talks over everybody and then he's very rude and I'm gonna I try to kick him off the time
Don't reprimand him. I mean, you know, you can say whatever he wants to say
You know, I'm gonna say whatever I want to say on my own platform in regards to whatever he has to say, but
He made me upset. Did you hear my?
Diatribe or my thoughts today in regards to you.
You'll be a good dad to somebody.
I was.
Aw, not fake.
To a human.
I loved it.
Holy shit.
Not necessarily my human, but somebody's human.
I think you would.
I think you're more than a cat daddy.
You and they got all the cats around you and whatnot.
It's just like, you know, I'm like, I'm like a posture.
Plus you are. You're very awful.
Not all of us, I am.
But I'm just a bitch. Let's keep it real.
Oh, I would not describe you as that except, you know,
in like the, I don't think the work is-
I put you through hell, didn't I?
Well, I mean it's like
We were back and forth if we were paying attention to each other and like watch you and like stuff, but um
I did. I'm sorry
I'm publicly acknowledging it right big lesson. You you put me through some stuff, but
I'm um, I don't know what I put her through but
I love you. I should have been born a male
in a wartime
Probably two generations ago. I would be very good at it. Yeah, I'm sorry
You're so funny. I'm sorry. Oh, you're sorry. Thank you. Thank you so much. I am
I'm very sorry
because I
Have all this
And it's it's it's a weapon
And it shouldn't be, but it is, but I'm sorry.
Cause I had to beat you down a little bit, sorry.
I'm sorry, but you survived somehow and it will survive again
If it up a good fight, and then it's like at the end of the day
Well, I mean that ending wise
You didn't deserve putting me and Tommy James having sex with you. Yeah, I can't a little bit ugly
But I have to like learn how to laugh at myself, you know, even in the memes, you know
It's like I was like much of your top yourself. I mean beat the shit out of me, man
I always want to like more like, you know, feel like it's a friendly friendly thing even like, you know
There's public things going on like
It'd be like, at least like, to like, kind of like be understanding, you know, otherwise.
Well, who are you going to be? Are you going to be cultist, like you're waking up?
Because you're going to be cult. I'm going to take over the cult.
Thank you, Marcy.
I don't even know right now.
Go to 11. Oh my gosh
You see the Rajneesh video. Oh, I don't know
You did not see it like it's a trippy kick trippy made it and I don't know if you ever watched that
I don't know if it's new channel. Oh
That the one with the whole whole thing going on. No, but I mean in a different way
Yeah in a different way. I mean, I feel like I have to go up against
What's that guy's name ghost
He hates me, so I'm gonna have to completely obliterate him, but I love God or Goddy that he's my favorite
She she don't know I mean how am I gonna destroy a cult of Goddy or God is a part of it
Well, let me try to maybe I can summon him. I'm not sure I do I do have a means to like, you know, maybe like I
Want to know what he looks like so bad yet
I don't want to know because it's such a mystery and then I have
Thing that is who can always pacify me when it comes to that so
I'm just gonna be a brat when it comes to all of it look I know I'm not gonna be
able to come back on your stream the way I am right now for a long time okay
but she was there all the time I normally don't say I love people but I do
love you oh thank you well I love you too and I might not say it tomorrow
It was sometimes we do change from day to day with nothing's a promise nothing
It is what you know, it's like but for this moment, I do mean it today
So flip it ship it. What are you guys done? Done seriously, but I mean it at this very
particular moment today. I guess it was a very short speeding moment, right?
And if you fuck me or anyone else I care about over,
I will destroy you!
And did she just say that in the film?
Well, I believe that, and you know,
I will respect that in the film.
And that's the Lilith within me.
Oh, it's the Lilith in her.
Yep.
See, and that's like another.
Oh no, I might've been possessed.
Me, maybe.
Oh gosh, yeah.
She's a devil and she literally I love it. I think I didn't think
Something about like talking to mr. Big Pipe's way before I met you or like I think maybe just
Well, you were talking about a lot of people that I've talked to before I knew about you from what I've done in my own little
miniscule research
Researching me Wow
Well, I have been like continuing to watch your show and it's like, now I like, you know, I'm really liking the episode.
Well, I was worried about you all day today as you're, you know, I'm not gonna say what I said to you privately or anything.
But you're not allowed, well, like the level that you're present online, you're not allowed to tell us when you're...
Well, you have to give us notice when you're going to be MIA missing in action because
I was worried about you all day today.
There are certain people who are in these online communities who know that I was worried
about you all day today and you can't do that to us anymore.
Please don't do that anymore.
I won't do that.
Please.
Because I know that you sit there like, oh, nobody cares about me. I want to kill myself
You better not kill yourself. We all do care about you tremendously and you're a game-changer
You know people give you a hard time. They razz you they haze you whatever the term is that they want to utilize
but we do love you very much and
Don't fuck that up, please
Okay, I will I'll try my best. I'll try my best, but you know
Not about try do or do not consider me Yoda
Star Wars
I'm that little green thing. I'm that little thing that that that little creature
Do or do not do not try
Seriously, can you do?
I think you can. You're smart. You're handsome. You're intelligent. You're, I mean, you're smarter than I am.
Oh shit.
Oh yes.
I love that. I'm smart, so maybe I make a lot of dumb decisions and maybe I'm like, but I do like, you know, but I think you're...
You're smarter than I am. You're more charismatic than I am. You're more intelligent than I am.
Things going on and I don't say that to anybody and you know that
You do
Why can't you accept that? Well, like why is this a thing? I do I do why is this a thing that is?
Where's the rhythm? Oh gosh for Goddy. That'd be great to say hi
It's like a portion like I don't know I want to talk to Goddy. He's my favorite
Yeah, he's my absolute favorite because I can't figure out what he looks like in my mind. I've tried
I can't figure it out
Well, he doesn't have to it doesn't matter
I'm here to talk to you. Yeah, thank you
Yeah, you're beautiful in your green screen. I don't look beautiful. I like crap right now. I'm drinking. I'm smoking outside
At some point I'm gonna walk outside. Have a cigarette. Um, I
Love you John. I
Do I mean did you hear that?
Look
There's some research he says
I know, where is Tibetan?
Oh, gosh, for Gotti.
That'd be great to split up to say hi.
Um, it's like, unfortunately,
like, I don't know if there's...
I want to talk to Gotti.
He's my favorite.
He's my absolute favorite.
Because I can't figure out
what he looks like in my mind.
I've tried.
I can't figure it out.
I did set up the, yeah, the link, but I love it.
He'll get it or something, you know.
Well, he doesn't have to, it doesn't matter.
I'm just here, I'm here to talk to you.
Yeah, thank you.
Well, yeah, you're beautiful.
And you're green screen.
I'm not only beautiful, I like crap right now.
I'm drinking, I'm smoking outside.
At some point I'm gonna walk outside and have a cigarette.
I love you, John.
I, I do. I mean, look, so it says, Crystal Marie, Crystal Marie says she says that I'm
being restrained. Who's been streaming? I'm being restrained, right?
I don't care what she's saying. I don't care who's restraining you either. I'm just talking
to you. Sorry, I'm sorry.
It's just you and me.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
No, why are you sorry? Like, what, like, you don't have to bow to me or anything. I'm
I'm just here.
A little bit stoned right now
because I got this, it's called a Pina Colada vape.
It's like a two gram vape right here.
It's like.
Oh yeah, a special vape.
Yeah.
The all-in-one, it's like comes already charged.
You know, it's disposable basically after it's done.
You just, it'll be all-in-ones and like.
Okay, well that's nice.
I had a smoke to the top.
Are you high on the vape or like, what is us vape?
I'm a little bit, I'm a little bit stoned.
Yeah, but I've been sleeping all day
but having weird dreams.
Actually, I mean, I had a dream.
Well, what did you dream about?
I had a dream that you had like a little dog.
And then it's like, we were kind of like out.
And then you got the dog.
Well, I was in the dream.
I didn't know you recently. Yeah, really the reason. Oh, well, I was a little dog. No, no, you had a little dog
Well, I used to have a little I used to have a little shits you a panda
That was me and panda and bear. Yeah, I
Had a little baby. You're walking this dog in the dream where we're kind of go. Oh, and you had this big like
You're kind of like a supervillain in the stream.
I have to go back to the stream where I talked about it.
Well, that makes sense.
Yeah.
You had the thing that you were just like compounded
like South America and you had all this property
is out there.
Yes, that's where I want to be.
Okay, this makes perfect sense because from South America,
you could easily go to Antarctica.
And that way I could get to where some other lands are.
because it might possibly be an accident.
No, that's killing a dog, but she had a little dog,
but then she didn't like anymore when it got to it.
I swall. So that makes sense. Okay.
I was in your power in this compound, and I was like, oh, no, and it's like, I thought
at least you played a, I was like, do you like Catwoman in the house?
So the Nazis, the Nazis are behind me.
Okay, that makes sense.
Okay.
What else is going on?
Are they hot?
I'm looking for hot Nazis.
Yeah.
They don't seem to be finding me.
I'm looking for them.
I'm looking for somebody, anybody's appropriate with.
So if you could help me, that would be great.
Okay, let's go with that.
I wish, I don't know, the thing that is
we usually find this show and he's like,
do you think, I think he might have been one
of your henchmen in the dream or something like, you know,
but it was kind of like the old school Batman's
where you were like.
I think that is, can I get his sperm?
I mean, I mean, I'm the first sperm
from willing donors of hot guys.
Can I get a list?
I'm checking it twice, trying to find out who's naughty or nice.
I mean, I'm trying to figure it out.
Help me, help me, help me, Mikey.
White Christmas.
Colt.
Awakens.
I don't know.
I don't even mean to be here.
I'm just, how am I here?
I feel like I'm in like a hand to mind box.
Like, like, why am I here?
Help me. I'm here. Give me something.
When I'm reading, I have some cards. I don't know.
I don't know. Give me a reading. Whatever you got.
Like, what do you have?
Okay. What do I got for you? Okay.
Look at the reading.
I don't know if I want to know.
But my hair looks nice today. I'm happy about that.
Low humidity. That's what happened.
Okay.
Okay. Like, let's see.
If only if only John would gain some way. I mean he looks like Hugh Jackman
If he would just gain some way I could rate them. Oh, I said that. Oh, my god. Oh, I'm sorry
Look, I came up first. It says the devil and the magician and of course, like, you know
I am the devil. Let's keep it real
Pretty magical thing that's almost like I'm almost like the magician binding the devil or something, but it's like
Let's keep it. I am Lucie bird. Just call me Lucy going forward
Well, you know the capricorn sign is represented with this tarot card, you know the side of capital
Well, we do I know I was saying Elvis, but I lied
We're the same birthday
I have to say something, try to make it go away, it didn't work, it didn't work, nothing worked, it's okay.
because opacucas probably does like you know make a difference in the thing.
It also because it doesn't make a difference. I tried everything and you didn't go away and you're
still here so you know you dominated me okay I'm like I'm here I'm the Robin to your stern
whatever but if that's the case you have to entertain me.
Okay, well here, with a special guest,
maybe I can entertain you.
Let's welcome a special guest.
This is a surprise guest.
Miracles can happen, can happen to you.
Bravo, this is beautiful, this is...
You see how God works?
You see how this works, everyone?
Take a good look, everybody.
Take a good fucking look.
This is how it should be, everyone.
I just saw this literally 10 seconds ago. I saw this. I couldn't believe my eyes. I said, let me go
This is fucking beautiful. I love this. Oh, no, you came on here and you have your
Avatar that I used to see in everything
Yes, this is this is good stuff. I'm so glad you came back. You guys are good now. Everything's good. I
Think so I but you confused me and I want to talk to you about that
All right, let's do this well because you didn't merge your energy with John or psyche
Maybe leeched a little off of me, maybe took a little bit from me, you know, we'd merge
I never attacked you though. No, and that's what's the beautiful thing. No and and
And and I and I wonder I
Wonder what you look like you never have to tell me. I wonder who you are
Oh, that's fine. I look like I look like this
No, you don't
No, you don't but I do wonder are you older than me or younger? That's the only thing I wonder
Are you older than me or younger than I'm 47? I'll be 40 this year
You're younger than me really. I'm a little younger. Yeah. Really?
I thought you were older than me because of how wise you sound. Like 60? No, no, I'm young. I'm young and wise.
Really?
Yeah, I lived a hard life.
We're well
Okay, the only question you don't have to answer if you don't want to what ethnicity are you the Italian?
No, you're are you really? I'm Italian. Yeah
Really? What do you thought you thought I was like?
Portuguese or something. No, I'm Italian. I think you're lying to me. I'm not lying to you
What I love open Italian
Well, I it doesn't you seem older to me older and not Italian. Okay
Yeah, no, this is me. I'm younger and Italian
Can I see you or no?
Yeah, yeah, one day you can see me, but not right now. No, you know, you never have to yeah, it's just cool
It doesn't make sense to me
No, no, it's okay. It will all make sense one day. No, we call cold mysteries. I know I know it's like an unsolved mystery
It's like the Bumir trying
I am I am you'll see no, I don't think you are
Yeah, but it's it's good that you guys are back together and this is going well. I love to see this
Where are you?
Right now. I'm in Chicago just outside of Chicago
How did you find Psyche John? How did I find him? Yes, we came I came to troll him
Not just him but the whole channel
from where
Just a random I think beat us first and then from beat us here
No, no, it was a beater mostly and then came here after that
Yeah, that's exactly what happened
No, you're you're not we saw you at a VB's
Psych we saw your VB's first never I've never well he's has he been on baby?
Yeah, yeah, he was at VB's and then from there it was beaters and then from beaters then he had his own stuff
We came here. Where do you live?
Just outside Chicago in Aurora. No, it doesn't sound good either
No, she's very skeptical today. No, I'm just listening to you. No, no, it's true
How many siblings do you have?
to
Younger or older
Younger and older
How tall are you?
Why are you on the internet?
To have a good laugh
I'm lying about that. What am I here for work? Oh, I'm working. I'm undercover
No, don't don't don't blow my cover
Not in a bad sense
I'm investigating somebody
No
But you do
No, I'm here to have a good time just like everybody else. I hope everybody's having a good time. You're supposed to be
What is your ethnicity?
Italian, you know your time, you know, you know where Italy is
Well, I'm not an idiot. I wasn't I wasn't born there. No, I wasn't born there. I was born here obviously my people
No, it's
All right, why do you tell me when you think why do you why do you conceal yourself?
There's no concealing. This is it. No, you you do
What do you think I am? What do you think I am? You think I'm Russian?
No, you're Indian
Indian I
Are you ever going to show yourself? I'm not gonna push
No, no, no, no, are you ever gonna show yourself ever? Yeah, I plan on doing a whole show on my channel
It's gonna be an hour long special. Yeah, I plan on having guests and everything and that's again. No, I just I can
I can and you're older than you clean
She's a smart one. It's like she's a small one, you know, she's very smart. I like your voice
I I did a stream talking about you today. I I can't
Decide in my mind what you look like
You liked me tonight. It's okay. I'm not mad
On a scale of one to ten. What do you think I look like?
And I'll tell you the truth. I'll tell you the truth. I'll tell you the truth. Are you stay the right number?
No, no, it's okay. I
Don't want I don't want you to lie to me or anything
I do like just know it would put a smile on your face. That's all
You do but don't lie to people. That's what I'm here for. That's what I'm here for at the end of the day
You're over 40. I know that
your
You are attractive. I
See that
But I don't know what you look like
I'll stop you when you're wrong
Do you have kids? No
Okay, have you been in love?
extensively
Y'all writing this down down there by the way, y'all fucking
That's why you talk it you're a liar there. Oh you see she knows all the tells
Why did you walk away? Alex? You're good. You're good at this. You're really good. No, why?
Well, why did you walk away from her cuz she did love you?
Why she didn't because she did exactly she did but she
lied but what what was the lie?
She lied about her love. So you were willing to forgive
You should have forgiven her. No, no, no, no, no, no, I shouldn't know I'm no
I'm correct and the reason I say that is
Because nobody's perfect and you were too innocent
That's what it was. I wasn't too innocent and
No, I don't forgive very easily. That's what it was
I won't argue. Yeah, so it was very easy to walk away. Are you ever gonna return? No
You should
This was a great night. By the way, this is great. I didn't expect this at all
What it what instigated this you came here?
Um, I love psyche very much, and he loves me very much, and it's what it is
Beautiful beautiful this has you know this has my blessing all the way
I love you because you let me in love him
and the only way I can love him is by loving you.
So it's kind of a package deal.
Beautiful.
We got to get back to basics.
We got to talk about aliens.
Comets from fucking...
Okay, let's talk about aliens.
We got to get back to all this stuff.
Okay, here's a question.
What do you think about Billy Carson?
He is the foremost speaker right now when it comes to extraterrestrial contact within
the ancient alien sort of realm.
That's like a popular thing.
He's actually from the same area of Florida that my mother is from.
I was kind of disappointed with the NASA thing. They didn't see shit on the dark side of the moon
With the fucking pictures they took and everything there wasn't like no bases. No, okay
Well, here's a question. Do you think the moon is natural or artificial? That's
I think it's that it's natural. I think it's natural
Okay, do you think that there's something on the dark side of the moon that we're not told about that's question number two
I am very skeptical. Yeah, I think there's something there and this whole thing was just like publicity stuff
Okay
Do you think that's a great aliens or the
Interesting beings with giant eyes are real or fraudulent
I think there's something, I don't know if it's the grays,
I think there's definitely something above what we are.
Well, it's definitely above, maybe,
well do you think that they could be parallel or below?
Technologically, they're definitely above.
And they might be from here,
they might be from Earth, like way back,
that went forward and kept us back, you know what I mean?
Like Antarctica might have a whole base over there.
Fucking like genius lizard man or some shit like that and they're keeping technologies like suppressed for us
You know slowly putting it out
Okay
Would you say that you yourself might be a
specimen of
interbreeding between
Things that are not of our realm versus what are?
Definitely possibility definitely
You sound like you are. Oh me personally you mean? Yes. Yes. I might be like elevated
Species. Yeah, you're right about that. I don't have a tail though. Well, I'm glad that'd be hard to hide
Yeah, that would be hard
Well, here's another question this is invasive do you think that John psyche is?
You might be because the way he thinks is not like other people you you've seen that for yourself
The way he puts things together the way he creates
It's totally different from any normal. Well, what about the way he looks?
You mean the hair? No. Oh, it's facial structure. No. Oh
He's lanky miss
Yes, they are known they are known to be tall and lanky. That's true. And sometimes he does get a little gray when he's not like
Washing up and stuff
And if you ever see these nails, oh my god, that's how other world be those nails sometimes well, I've met him in person
Do you know that? Um, if it's if a human were to be born on Mars
His proportions would be the norm
To what if what somebody will be the averages on earth? Oh, it's how you mean
He's about six three and I'd say about maybe
160 pounds am I correct?
I'm a few pounds less than that, I think, but...
One fifty?
Okay.
Six three, but...
Have you ever seen...there's a movie.
Oh, I don't want to talk to ghosts.
I really don't.
I know, not after today, so I'll leave.
No, no, no.
I kicked him off.
There's a movie called The Space Between Us about a young man who was born on Mars.
who actually, the actor that they chose,
who was his biological father,
looks a lot like Psyche.
It's very interesting to me.
I think like...
Have you ever seen, have you ever seen that movie?
Psyche.
The space between us. I'm gonna show you something and then I'm gonna go because I want your friend goes to come on here
But I don't want to ever talk to him again in my life. I actually got to take off Alex. It was great seeing you
Psych I'm so glad for you. You guys definitely, you know, do this again, please. This is
Ghosts what one day in some secret way show me I
wanted
See you. I wanted
You don't have to I just it's got it. It's got it, but you will you're definitely
You have to block me by the way, you're younger than so you're younger than I'm younger. Yeah, I am younger really
Yes
Yeah, a few years younger, but you look younger than me. No, I don't you do you you definitely do
Thank you for talking to me though anytime Alex just unblock me in your chat and I already
Okay, I don't believe you though
You will you will trust me you will I don't I'm never gonna believe you. I think you're lying, but it's okay. I
Will see you guys
Have a great night you two. All right. I'll see you guys. Take care
Be good
I like him. I like him.
Yeah.
No, I want to, I want to show you something psychic.
Just give me a moment.
Have you ever seen that movie?
Space Between Us?
Yeah.
No, I don't think I've ever seen it.
Really?
I don't know.
How can I watch that movie with you?
There's ways to like I want to show you. Oh gosh. I feel like people are lying to you about something. I don't like it.
Yeah. Yeah, movie night. But you see movies on on just court or you can jump like backstage and stuff, you know, where it's like not streaming on YouTube.
No, I'm gonna show you something.
let me go on google maybe it probably doesn't matter
let's check it out though we're watching we're watching a bunch of movie
previews the other night do you think then do you think that your friend was telling the truth
I think he was like one of my first songs I made but I have some gaudy songs or whatever
and I don't think I ever properly animated him but I did a few songs.
I don't believe him I normally like I'll take for granted what certain people say I don't
He's like, you know, bluffing, he's probably, he keeps his cards close.
No, I've thought about it, and I've tried to envision in my mind, I think, and maybe
there's a reason.
I think he's about 67 years old.
I've chilled like and I think that he's very nice. I think that he has at least three grandchildren
And I think that he just doesn't want anyone to know who he is
I did like draw this picture of him
Picture I drew that like oh, that's what you think you will wait. Let me I'm going now. Okay
Is this did I screen copy properly probably?
Well, I don't think I
Know keep it on the on the camera. I
Want to I want to take a picture. Okay. No, I think he does have a big beard
like I think it's more like what like
Five o'clock shadow
That he probably rocks something like that. I think that he has an olive complexion
I think that he went in his youth was a very good-looking guy.
Sorry, Jen.
In my youth, I was a very good-looking woman, not so much now.
But I think that he was beautiful.
There's my J-dog.
Where's he J-dog?
No, I don't like him.
I don't want to listen to him.
Sorry, sorry.
It's okay.
I just don't want to look at him anymore.
This one's a good one.
I like to end it in my feelings.
I, uh, is that picture of the person with the big eyebrow accurate?
Ah!
Did you ever see?
Well, actually, he was, like, his image is out there and he does have these, like, dark
eyebrows and he's like, uh, but it's, you know, it's like, well, someone like him, here's
what I would say, somebody like him, if he's, if that's an accurate picture, it is probably
not.
Okay.
We're going to take a little break from this.
We have a guest.
So, you're like, how are you chilling, bro?
My girl just cooked me steaks and asparagus.
Oh, lucky boy.
Hey, I was on some stream with some black guy named, um, wait a second, I'm pretty sure
you know.
It was like ship something. It was like some black guy Joe Shippley
No shamp something you replied to yourself. Oh
Wait a minute
It was Brian Rizzle in my child. I should lower that down. I'm sorry
Okay
There was somebody some blood. It was some black at my homie Brian Rizzle. Send me the link
It was supposedly some blood or something.
It was in SSI? SSI?
I don't know. No, it was Jimmy.
Oh, Joe, Joe. Groovy, Groovy Jimmy.
Yeah, with the black guy with a banana rum his name. Yeah, I know groovy Jimmy like he's like he's not a real blood
He's not a real man. I mean, I don't really know. I'm like he was on my show one time before I didn't end the live
Yeah, I didn't in the lives. Yeah, um, he um, I went to his channel once like his beat is like
Oh come to groovy Jimmy's I went over there and then all of a sudden I'm being doxxed
I'm being like my channel's being copyright based my chest say he's a he's a cop my child was saying he's a cop
A cop?
Yeah, my chat was saying he was a cop.
I don't know, but I know that he, like, you know,
RG and Barry went and drove by his house,
and then he, like, had a gun out,
and they tried to run each other.
Yeah, he's been targeted. That's not a good thing. Yeah. Yeah. Well, I know other we should stay away from we will
But they don't like him. They mean they attack him. But yeah, I know there
I don't know what I know. Hey, that's that doesn't involve you. Yeah, I know doesn't involve me at all
Yeah, exactly. So I'm sitting away from that guy. Stay away from the energy. Can you protect me?
Fuck yeah. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Let's eat some I have
Hey, look what I got.
I just went to McDonald's, guys.
Hey, Psyche, what did one day where I'd take you and my girl
we eat some IHOP together breakfast?
IHOP?
I'm down.
I like IHOP.
What you doing now?
Right now?
I'm just hanging out.
I'm having some fries.
I love you, Psyche.
You're the only real one.
Let's, Psyche, you got fries.
All right, Colin.
You got the bed?
You got to get the bed, Psyche.
Get the bed.
Oh, whoa, you were on Betus Pound tonight.
Yeah, I was kicking in with Betus.
Did you see Nancy on the stage?
Because Nancy said she was on her panel.
You were on the panel?
Yeah.
On the show.
And then they didn't want to hang out because they're too
serious.
Yeah.
Well, they are you know, they're not they're scared of
Sexuality they're scared. Well, I mean you think her bush is so big. It's like, you know drawing people in there
But yeah, but that's not my problem. You see like your bitch
You got a big bush and then me and all my people are trying to flirt with each other like
Figure yourself out before you'll be here putting yourself out there like I know you have a you have a you have a
I'm more smart, like you gotta let people believe in
to whatever they want, and that's it.
I do, I don't, I never push beliefs on anybody, you know?
Don't force nobody.
I don't, oh, you mean about sex?
Or anything about their feeling about it,
don't force nobody.
I don't force you, did I ever force you?
I know you, nope.
Take it.
Yeah, I wouldn't make an issue.
I know you're like a couple of times because I've been getting drunk.
Yeah.
But that's okay.
But I don't give a fuck.
I know my limits.
It's joking around.
And the thing is, it's like, you know, on my show, I joke around.
They over there fucking around.
In real life, I'm a perfect gentleman.
I mean, I respect people around you.
Yeah.
All times.
Yeah, and especially, you know, and I did meet this person where we were talking about earlier
I met her in person and I was completely respectful to her and then she said she thought I was gonna
Unalive her something on the on the meeting and stuff and then I mean all kinds of stuff. I mean, it's so ridiculous
I'm not and she said oh
Everyone needs to get restraining order against me because I'm a dangerous person. I'm gonna like I've never heard a person
My life anybody. I know it's crazy, but that's your family. Yeah
Yeah, well, she's putting it all over the all over the
the web and videos and stuff with the video.
Hey, bro, I was over there.
I was at, bro, I went to the fireworks show at Southgate.
How was that?
I took my girl to the fireworks show,
and I took my little kitty, my white cat.
Southgate.
I was going to take her to the Rondondo Beach one,
but then.
I went to the Redondo Beach one too early
and there was a bunch of white people
and I was like, babe,
we're not about to get hang here.
Oh, no, no, no, no, I'm like, real shit.
I was like, there's too many white people,
too many Americans.
If you're gonna be gone,
know the pier at around like, you know,
three o'clock in the afternoon on a Friday night.
Yeah, there's too many white people,
white, wavy and fucking American flag.
And I was like, babe.
Let's go back to South Central and celebrate it, and she was like, you're right.
I'm like, I'm the one driving, anyways, I'm gonna take you back, and I took her to Southgate.
Southgate is a Hispanic whitewash area.
It's not, it's not, Southgate is half whitewash.
So we had a good time.
We ordered corn dogs and everything.
You're a pretty Americanized Mexican person, aren't you?
Like, oh.
I'm not a hater.
You're pretty American.
You know, like there's a lot of like,
American their parents are Mexican but they're born here and they don't even
know Spanish and they don't know hardly. That's your problem if you you can
bitch out you got to hold your ground that's what America's about right? America
is about holding your ground right. Stay in my ground. Stay in your ground and then
Yeah, I mean like you know, I had somebody bitch out recently. We all know who that was but I'm not I mean I'm talking about
You be heavy man or what boyfriends there was no I haven't I mean I really have not I've never been dated
I've never really dated it. I even like a guy
The only one that's done to hang out with you. Yeah, my good
Yeah, Q said the only the closest he wants to get to me is like through the panel like on the TV
And then actually like you know and then for what he says some weird reasons
i don't know i think i think i'd probably be my head would probably be on like uh
exactly we really hang out around the beach i already got you on my instagram we can hang out
yeah be cool right yeah i wrote you back right i wrote you back to say hey yeah
okay it's good okay so we're all we're all said that that's the best way to do it is like instagram
we're too real these people are fake yeah and we're real people in a fake world i mean that's
But uh, yeah, I want to hear you what you gotta say, bro. I gotta say is that I'm like, you know
Yagtown, it's not yagtown. Come on. You know, you know, he says yeah, what is that? Oh, E and J or
Where's the Bartles and E and J is like I was going through a bro. I bought I spent like three hundred dollars in a thrift store
Did right there right there by our redondo beach. They got a lot of good stuff, huh?
I only bought like three shirts.
It's expensive, $100 shirts.
And a thresh shirt.
Yeah, I got the good ones though.
I know what I'm looking for though.
My friend used to go into thrift stores
and she had her trick was to look at all the pockets
and sometimes she'd find like $100 billets.
To the pockets.
To the pockets, man.
Oh please.
No, you don't like drugs psyche. I like weed and my my my like mushrooms
I like mushrooms. I have like there's there's something in my bait
But it's like if I buy a bar of chocolate and I visit you with my girl and my cat
Would you eat some other chocolate? Yeah, hell yeah, I love much. I like mushrooms. I've done them and uh
and I have like I know what to watch too when you watch that I know like the
trippiest things to watch you should hang out so my girl's down my girl says
she's down like kicking with you she had fun we definitely have fun like uh
she likes you because you're not you're not weird you're normal
we're not you know also like um
My dad was, he did a lot of contracting and so,
and he had, he dealt with like a lot of people
of different races, but he loved Hispanic people.
And when he's-
He's like, you ever watched the What's Up Rockers movie?
Uh-uh, I heard of it.
That's your people shit. What's the rockers the movie? You should watch that shit. No, I heard of a day without Mexicans
I heard in the world goes to shit. That was like 20 25 movies. That's last year. It's only last year. Yeah
20 20 like
I was born 81 I'm an 80s baby. I'm an 80s baby. So I'm old
So you never watch the what's up rocker movies? What's up rocker? No, I never heard of that. No
Can I show it? Can you look it up? Yeah, you're running the stream. What's up rocker?
Yeah, what's some rockers?
It's just like W. A. S. S. Up rockers
Okay, you see
Is there is it a movie?
No, it's a movie. It's a whole movie from South Central kids. Okay, let me see
Okay, I see the trailer you want to see the trailer play it bro play it and then you can see where I'm coming from
Central baby
Is your graffiti in this movie, I think you're a tagger right it's awesome
your skateboard okay that happens to have a can of spray paint okay I got you
hold on one second hey Sherry I'm going to I'm doing it I'm doing it buddy I'm
doing it here we go so I'm right here it's just fun bro you guys this is where
guys didn't learn how to be fun they just give up uh oh okay here we go
I live in the ghetto.
It's crazy down there. You can't be walking on the streets.
It's like a young, uh, turn of the globe.
Are you close to those guys?
I grew up, bro.
I mean, like, are you guys like nice friends?
I grew up. I didn't want to grow up like this.
You all the same?
This life gave me lemon, and I made lemonade.
What are you doing here in Beverly Hills?
That's it. That's where the white girls live you guys are so fucking like the Mexican remote or something
You little shit's a fucking lion
You know the lawn here. Why?
Have to get you out of here before the police gets you
Oh yeah, that's like his dad, that's like his dad's shooting at us, that's like his dad was sitting in his big ass mansion and shot him at us.
We say what's up rockers, everything.
What's up rockers?
They say what's up rockers.
That's called me.
It's pretty good.
What do you mean it's pretty good?
That shit blew up.
You see when I was like, I forgot the guy's name, but when I was a kid I watched, um, I watched kids, Larry, I guess it was Larry Clark or something, but there was another guy.
Let's join up Clumsy. Let's join Clumsy. Clumsy is waiting for us.
He's waiting for us? I don't think Clumsy likes me very much, but he doesn't like you or me either.
Hey Clumsy, why, hey, psyche, why do we like our gay activities together? Why is that?
Because we were comfortable or secure in ourselves. You can laugh about it. I'm not insecure. I know you're not
No, no, we are so secure. That's what I said. We're so we're so secure that we don't know
I just said to those down nobody gonna tell me otherwise right psyche, right?
Well, I mean, I'm not gonna tell you otherwise. You be holding that shit down for years. Yeah
Like I think that people like
Do it and this I'm gonna do right right. I mean, I just be I just want to be it's like I don't think
You know people can be whoever they want to be really I mean as long as they're not you don't need explanations
Yeah, exactly.
Sure, bro.
You've been doing this shit for how many years?
10 plus years?
Streaming?
Or what, being gay?
All this shit, whatever.
Whatever, though.
I've been doing it.
I'm the 300 glow that's just joined up,
and they didn't give a fuck either, though.
I was like, I'm going to join up.
Hey, baby, this is what I'm throwing, and this is what it is.
And then Psyche is like been doing this, I'm down with, I'm down with, I'm, I'm okay with my sexuality. I don't care.
But keeping it real is different.
I know, I know, John Stockton, I'm sorry, clumsy is like, you know, anything with, but I think
I don't know people a lot of people are just judgmental about that so we will be watching all the brand-new videos today
You can go back and like look at the videos and see I like kicking around fucking Manhattan Beach
Yeah, man. I'm just nice. I live in so I'm next to Hermosa Beach, which is like where they have like a lot of the
It's right there.
Yeah, it's right there.
It's right there and then Manhattan's next to.
That's where I take my girls and my little cats
and you just disturb my peace with my little cats right there.
It's over nigga.
Have you ever been to a restaurant called Fleming's?
There's one called Fleming's in Manhattan.
I went to the restaurants on the Redondo Beach Pier.
I went to the, to the pizzas.
The pizza lady, she's from Wallahara, the pizza lady right at the pier, she's from Wallahara, she's from my dad's hood.
So, we were over there, we bought pieces and she let us dance and everything.
She let Dina and my sister dance because we pulled up when my sister and my, and my girl,
they were dancing and having a good time.
Mm-hmm.
Oh, fun.
Yeah.
I'm right down the pier.
I'm the right down the pier.
The ladies.
Yeah.
There's a bunch of bars, restaurants.
There's a lot of, you know.
You know where the blonde hair Mexicanos come from?
From Malajara.
Jalisco.
Oh, they do.
That and she was make she makes is the pizzas right there still she's still making pizzas right now
She is
How do you say pizza in Spanish?
Pete don't know pito. Yeah, pito nigga. That's what you want to call it
Yeah, I don't care what you want to call it. You call it cock dick. Oh my god
Oh, whatever you want to call it. Oh, you mean big pinga or I'm not I don't care what you want to call it psyche
I'm not tripping. I really like you. I like you too. We're friends. We're friends and like now. We're we're more than friends
Oh, okay. I like you. I really really have to treat you some way. I'll treat you some way
Smack me around. I love it
If you were my friend, I would just fuck you up. I mean like you're my friend
I could be true, but we're friend. We're more than friends. We could wrestle we could wrestle and
And then you're gonna lose you're gonna be on top. Okay. Yeah
Mind losing I'm trying to be nice psyche. I know I'm not gonna wrestle with you
I'm not gonna wrestle why you make us hate all the time. What's going on?
I don't know. I'm always the one be the one trying to be nice, huh?
Yeah, well, you know John I wasn't exactly wasn't exactly a friendship. It was more like
I wanted him to like reveal the truth. It's not a friendship. Oh, yeah, it's not even a true now
It's like now. He's gonna not please never watch some like fucking real
Kings versus kings. You never watch
Psyche believes in that shit. Yeah
Tina England kings these things are kings. They're God
Well, yeah, I do come from royalty. A lot of a lot of Europeans come like, you know, everyone, I believe in that shit. Yeah. I do have a bit. I know, I know, I know.
Oh, John Stockton, I know I've had. Well, it's like friends. It's like that's taking a little bit too much. What happened? I believe I believe in royalty.
This is why all the fellow signal fellow, I believe in royalty.
Oh, I'm better than you.
Oh, nobody's better as long as you are.
Exactly.
We're all humans, like no one's an ant, people.
So someone's saying, she says she doesn't talk about me,
but she was talking.
I know Bita always talks about me.
She has a big mouth.
I don't still have anything to talk about.
Yeah, she likes you.
Bita is actually likes you.
She does?
I know.
Well, she's like to me.
Because Bita is the only one that's real,
but she kind of explained it though.
She can't. And she like, um, yeah, I've heard her like, you know, like, like one time she
said, okay, if she was going to try to say Samman's live, but she said, okay, I think
Psyche's live now go to Psyche's and they're like, you mean Samman? And she's like, oh,
she can't explain it. Why?
Yep. We all make mistakes guys. I've made mistakes, but you know what? I learned. I grew up.
You're a good-looking man, huh? That's what it is.
I'm okay. I mean, I think I'm okay. I don't think I'm like terrible.
You are a good-looking man.
Thank you so much.
You're a good-looking guy.
Exactly.
I do have good hair and like, you know, it's funny like all the all the things being made about me
I'm like, I'm like balding and I'm like, I think there's enough to make fun of me without making me bald and like
You know, like trying to make me sirex. I'm not sire. There's a big difference like a huge difference between me and sire
First of all, sirex isn't my species. He's like a goblin person. You know, second of all, I'm not retarded third of all
I have my teeth. First of all, I have full head of hair fifth of all. I'm good-looking sixth of all
I don't like transgenders or good
leaving catfish by transgenders constantly.
I mean-
The main thing, you have hair.
You know, most of these older people don't even have hair.
Right.
And that's okay.
I like-
You don't even have swag.
There's a really good looking bodybuilder
that I like a lot.
And he took off his beanie and he's bald,
but I was like, hey, you made bald beautiful.
What bodybuilder is that?
His name is Godbody Reigns.
And he's like-
Godbody Reigns?
Uh-huh.
He's on YouTube. He's really good. He's really cool. Yeah. God body. Yeah. God body. G-O-D-B-O-D-Y. And then R-E-I-G-N-S.
Kind of slow. R-E-I-G-N-S, I think.
he comes right I think he comes up let me see I'll put I'll put the oh yeah god body reigns
yeah do you see him oh my god there's your boy there's a lot of porno and when I type that in
the there's your boy yeah you see him he's like harry kind of harry in the all right can you look
Oh, the strength cartel. Yeah, I know strength cartel. They have my boy. Yeah. I am my my mom lives right there. My people live there. I like the guy. There's like spy boys in that. And there's this guy. No, strength cartel. The main head is my boy. Oh, that's a big guy, right? He's like really big.
Yeah, it's like he's my little cousin. You're not listening. I'm listening to you. You're awesome
But okay, so do you know who Mexican monster is because is he related to YouTube? No, I'm from the Mafia
He's down. Yeah, he just says he knows how to do his thing. He does. Oh, they're really successful
I mean, it's like people and then I'm the mafia and then these foods to these foods are pretty they asked me
They're like a you were good. We're good
Yeah
Sigh, don't ever tell nobody about this. All right
Well, this is on this is on national. Oh, well. Yeah, I'll tell them but they'll find they'll find us
Look it up. Look it up. That's my boy. I've seen it. I've seen them. That's my cousin, bro
Me and my mom already got beef with my cousin. I'll show everyone a picture of the bag
I'll show everyone a picture. I'll play the video
Well, I know I'm allowed to play the videos, but hold on I can show you I can show this best of the best
I'll play a minute of it for a period of time.
Hey, psyche, I'll spare you.
Okay, you tell your cousin I'm allowed to play this, okay?
Thank you so much.
No, you're okay to play with it.
Okay, I'll play it.
I'll play it.
Nobody cares about you.
Oh, come on.
Okay, here we go.
We're stronger.
Here, this is it.
Play it.
Whoo!
Just pulled up.
Play those, baby.
Time to play.
Get that one.
What's up, Psyche? What do you see?
Whoa, whoa, what's going on here?
Psyche likes this shit. Look at Psyche.
He's so impressed.
Hey, Psyche, what's this?
You can't do that shit, how's it be?
I can barely lift the butt.
That gives movement.
You can't even carry that bar home, man.
You can't carry the bar bar.
Then you can't be so tensed.
You can't carry this. You can't be part of the team, Tikey.
Why are you acting like this is not what's going on?
Tikey, why are you acting like this is not what's going on?
You can't carry this. You're not part of the team.
Okay, that's good. Wow.
You see what I'm saying? Tikey, if you can't pick it up, you're not part of the team.
Why are you pretending?
I can pick up at least 60 pounds, but I did pick up the bag of 60 pounds ain't shit.
I know I'm gonna look at my arm. I'm just like a skinny guy.
You smoke, man.
Oh shut up.
Listen, we're smoking meth last night, bro. Shut up. You're silly. You was and then you're gonna kick me out cuz you hate me
You were smoking mad in front of this stop it stop it nobody
Stop it
Stop it. All right, my girl has roofies. She wants to root be us together. Are you
Hey, you're down to take drugs together. Am I good?
Smoke weed. No, you're not bitch.
I'm a pussy, bro. I'm gonna call you out. Okay, call me out. Hey, let's talk about
You're already getting pulled out. You're a sellout. Okay, get out here. It's jerk
The trip the date is off
Get out. I mean, geez
Look at these people. Okay, let's get back to the Alice stuff. I mean good lord
And I say, don't say that.
There's people that actually believe this shit.
Geez.
I'm having enough problems without fucking this shit.
Okay.
Uh-oh.
Oh, that's the wrong channel.
Okay.
Oh, no, no, it's not.
Here, video.
One thing I'm not, I'm not a sellout,
I'm not a fucking, not a lot of, a lot of the names
they like to call me, but don't, don't fucking slander me
out of my name right now.
Have been up problems. Okay in this. Yeah, he started calling me names or he started like accusing me of stuff
Oh, that's cool Nancy. I'll check it out. Maybe I'll check on on the Facebook. Maybe I'll check it out
We're watching a bunch of movie
Previews the other night. Do you think do you think that your friend was talking the truth?
Do you think that he is?
Younger
I don't believe him
I think he was like one of my first songs I made with I have some gaudy songs or
whatever and I don't think I ever properly animated him but I didn't do
a few songs. I don't believe him. I normally like I'll take for granted what
certain people say. I don't believe him.
He's like you know bluffing. He's probably his car is closed. No, I I've thought about it and and I've tried to envision
And my mom's over the cooker's nest. She's confused. I think and maybe there's a reason. And the reason. I think he's about 67 years old.
I'm chilled like and I think that he's very nice. I think that he has at least three grandchildren
And I think that he just doesn't want anyone to know who he is
I did like draw this picture of him
Sure, I drew that like oh, that's what you think you will wait. Let me I'm going to okay
What is it? Did I screen cop it properly? Probably not.
Well, if I don't think I do.
I love it.
But no, keep it on the camera.
I want to take a picture.
Yeah.
No, I think he does have, I don't think he has a big beard.
Like, I think it's more like, like, um, five o'clock shadow.
that he probably rocks something like that.
I think that he has an olive complexion.
I think that he, in his youth, was a very good-looking guy.
In my youth, I was a very good-looking woman,
not so much now, but I think that he was beautiful.
Where's my j-dog? Oh, no, no, no. No, I don't like him. I don't want to
Sorry
Yeah, I was drawing this woman. I don't know if it was Shannon. No, like what do you think's gonna happen for you?
What is it going to happen for me?
Well, I think that I'm going to come to some,
hopefully some breakthrough with my show
or with like some side business that like it comes up
and like I'm going to keep trying to just like, you know,
make some money.
Do you think you're going to sell out or be genuine?
I'm always going to be genuine.
I always be myself, but it's like, it's kind of like,
I do want to like be able to,
I have a supplemental income, so I'm not like sitting without money here like I'm not eating on days and stuff like that so
Well, you have some money you're you're you're not done
I spent everything on we eat and so like you know
You're spending money on supplement all things that you don't really need yeah
But at least we don't really worry.
Well, it's okay.
I mean, we all figure out our life, like, ways to make money to assist in what we need in
different ways.
Like, when I got this thing from you, I'm going to be sleepy, I'm going to go to bed, but really,
mechanically and biologically smarter than I am you just are and I don't say
that to many people because they could be my enemy if I just say that but I'm
saying to you because you are not my enemy you're my friend I hope you are at
least but where I say you are stupid is that you don't use your brain enough
You do have the skill set. You're definitely not. You're as far from an idiot as could be.
And I don't understand why you hinder yourself like you do.
It actually hurts my feelings that you hinder yourself as much as you do.
I know I'm not the only person who has come around and they're like, hey, let's make something cool
And then you kind of like
currently
Fuck it up to an extent and I mean if I was in my 20s doing this
I wouldn't give a shit 30s and maybe but now I'm almost fucking
fucking years old
Coming across you and here we are
Why?
That's my question.
Because you're a beautiful soul.
I mean, I look at you,
and I'm so in love with you
in the most broad of sense.
I mean...
That's how I know I've even evolved and developed within myself
Look when I love somebody somebody fucks with them. Oh, I'm I'm just a
I'm Lenore
We have a mystery I don't understand
You'd like to talk to a mystery guess it depends on who it is if it's somebody out like I want to talk
Okay, okay, I'll take them off if you don't want to talk to them. Okay, if it's somebody don't want to talk to
I'm just gonna go and I'll say well, let me say good night now
I'm gonna tell you beforehand
Tell me before
Okay, cuz I don't want to talk to anybody I don't want to talk to you
I'm just here to talk to you, but I'm happy that guy came on cuz I really
I really like talking to whoever that is a lot, but I don't want to talk to anybody.
Yeah, I was hoping Alexander McQueen.
Okay, I'm sorry. I'm going to stop. I'm sorry. I didn't know my microphone was off.
Hey, 22 people. Listen, so she's written an essay, I guess.
It says, for INX and Psyche, streaming is their lifeline.
Both are dependent on these communities, whereas I am not.
Okay, hold on.
And then it says, oh shit, hold on, there's more.
It says, here's Richard's beginning.
Okay, so INX went full force in regards
to defending Brandon and has spoken to him
since that point and passed my private personal info to him.
She also pointed him to sources online
that would assist him in maliciously attacking,
harassing, slandering, and bullying me.
INX has been leaving me multiple hateful videos
or hateful voicemails weekly, hold on.
Weekly.
Since he the app for mentioned stage and psyche has created a hate campaign against me despite my generous donations
I
Was the hate can't I started a hate campaign against her I have I don't think so
I was I defended her to the end. I defended her to the end up until today
I was still like, you know, she'll you know, but you know not anymore. I gave her one more
I gave her a final final chance listen to this
it says
RG, aka Black RG, mentions Psyche having a sexual attraction to Brandon.
He was correct.
It's specifically the rough, degrading talk and humiliation Brandon engaged in in the
past live stream, asking if his target wants to be assaulted as a SA.
Also, Psyche is attracted to Brandon's effeminate, youthful face.
Psyche is intimidated by Ganville.
I know this for a fact.
Intimidated!
I don't like him. Gamble appears to be trying to cover something about a few nefarious women in these communities
That's my issue with him and I will cover the situation in a further stream
There is a way to document on YouTube the band Brandon footage
I likely will in the future, but it's important to note that Gamble and his group did record it and it's entirely initially
And it's entirely initially and it's available on platform to just kick and rumble what she's a problem with me playing that video
Let's see, INX has been leaving multiple hateful voices weekly since the aforementioned stage
and Psyche has created a hate campaign against me despite my generous donations to him, which
was a factor that led to me opting to point out his rather disturbing history.
Oh, it's because Brandon was modded in my chat for like a day and started releasing
some disturbing voicemails of INX, Psyche has likely heard them, but he's still friendly
with her, primarily likely due to her knowledge of certain people in the streaming communities
he seeks to exploit, stalk, blackmail and extort using his stream as a front.
But also, due to him knowing, she's a large dollar amount donator.
high level of entitlement and seeks money without having to authentically work for it.
Ganvel and Barb Sawyer pointed Crystal Anne to have extensive past videos of Brandon,
a few of which I hadn't seen and posted the link in Crystal's chat,
which is comprised of a large audience, to an off-YouTube platform. Anyone who wasn't aware
of the past videos of Brandon became aware at that stage due to Crystal's vast online presence.
I threw away Brandon way before you did, like, you know, and then you get mad at me like I was not talking to Brandon.
I had no communication with them until until you started turning on me, right?
Gamble appears to be trying to cover. Let me see. It's okay. So we got that part. We got that part.
So I don't know what this is. Who wrote this essay? I'm wondering.
Psyche initially convinced me to give Brandon a chance.
I did not say give Brandon a chance.
I said I was going to.
I didn't say anything about her.
I didn't say, I'm not going to try to convince her of anything.
I'd exposed Brandon previously to a certain level.
you years ago in Relarges of Vegan Patria and I'd seen the Omega or Monkey Up clip that
featuring a little 13 year old. I've interviewed Brandon once with Psyche and then a gaming
stream with Brandon and INX. Psyche didn't like the backlash she received due to Brandon and dropped
him due to public pressure. No, it was because Brandon called me fucking stupid and several
times on the stream and she knows this, I talked to her right after. But it turned out to be a
blessing in disguise because it revealed the disingenuousness of Psyche, which
led to my completely cutting him out and his toxic associates out of my life permanently.
I let Samman on my panel and Brandon flipped the switch on me, but I'll keep in mind,
but keep in mind, I'd already seen the level of negativity and aggression with him,
so I wasn't completely unexpected from my perspective. Okay, so she was intensifying it, wow.
Okay, Brandon attempted to intimidate and dominate me shortly after because he misread
my kindness for weakness, and he's used to engaging in such behavior with women
and his other targets who are generally vulnerable individuals.
I mean, where does it get to like how does that do with me in any way? I don't know and what what so so yes
I didn't convince her. I so it was my fault. I convinced her to give him a chance
No, I never said give Brandon a chance. I said I said I'm gonna wait
I'm gonna wait to make a judgment until I know more and I want him to reveal himself also
But she did you guys if you see I let him talk shit about me and then I would put him up on full screen
So you can, so you can see, I mean, it's like, and you talk, I would just expose him, but it's like,
anyway, or people will expose themselves. I completely cut Brandon off, discontinued all
direct communication and blocked him from my social media. He's tried to contact me since,
but I ignore him. A day or so ago, Psyche could reconnect with Brandon and INX for several
live streams spanning multiple days. I disconnected from them, both entirely and
severed all associations. No, not until, yeah, okay, INX demonized me in conjunction with Psyche,
Well, I don't know. So anyway
Yeah, she's on and off switch. Sometimes she's smart about things other times
She's a dumb dumb, you know, I mean, it's like she when she said I'm smarter than her. She probably was right
I mean, I don't know. It's like she's not very being very logical or anything right now. She's being
Crazy acting crazy. She's fucking saying claiming. She's the devil, you know her eyes are rolling in the back of her head
She's she's doing rituals on on on the camera, you know without without but I mean that'd be fine
But if like, you know, you say you're a Christian you can't really say you're the devil you're a witch
You're an alien it's like Christians are usually like, you know, I'm humbled under Jesus and stuff like that
But okay, whatever whatever. I don't think she's gotten to the New Testament yet
I don't think she cares much for Jewish people when she finds out Jesus was Jewish
She's gonna fucking have a shit bit
Um, but, you know, what can I do about that? Right? Um, a big fucking problem. I'm the big problem,
right? It's like, and all I said, and she didn't read the cease and desist either, because I said
that in the cease and desist, it didn't say completely cease and desist mentioning me and I
very, very, very serious charge.
Don't put that with my name.
And then that was it.
And so then she just goes to like doxing other people
and saying, I'm like really,
it's like, it doesn't really make much sense.
So, but you know, let me see,
I'm gonna do, I'm just gonna look at one more thing.
I mean, I mean, it's like,
I'll just see if there's anything I can,
I think I'll just get her other tweet
where she calls on the KKK to destroy her enemies.
How about that one?
as a little finale for tonight, a grand finale.
And Alex, I would not have done this
if you would have just not pushed me so far
and so cruel and been so, so crazy and like a pit bull.
And it's like, I just need to like, you know,
put the leash on the pit bull and, you know, we'll see.
So I'm just gonna read a little,
or I'll just, I'll get this last one, hold on.
And this is just, I have more.
But I'm not listen. I'm not gonna I'm not I'm not gonna stoop to her level and and dogs her family
But I have her family's dogs, you know, I bet I could but I wouldn't
So I'm not that kind of person. She is okay. Don't forget that
okay
she went low and
What and what and she didn't really explain? Oh, I'm just a all she has all she can do is he's broad broad
Slanders like there's no there's no evidence. It's all bullshit. I mean it's like so silly. So let's see what happened here
Let's see what happened. So we can go to kind of I can I mean, I just know I know I just I know I've
Seen back years
Of what's been going on. Okay, and there's things I could say
And I'm sure she does not want me to say and I wouldn't say them some nice
But my nicest has a limit
Okay
And I'll show this one last tweet and I'm not gonna say this side this tweet is not from today
It's not from a month ago a week ago. It's it. This is probably years ago
I'll tell you when the tweet was posted. It's posted back in
Let me see it now, but
Yeah, we do know that she called upon
The clan and stuff. Let me see
Then she got involved with IP to then she started calling them
You know Nazi network
Court cases court cases. Okay. She tweets about Trump for help. Oh, yeah, so
She is threatened. Okay. So, so here's an opinion. This is an opinion piece, but you know
Oh, maybe I do have the tweet
The woman is a serious danger could really end up the next mass shooter. She has threatened it many times on twitter
And the feds have even been to her mother's house where she lives and tweeted about that also
She is a never-checked class being a black libtard with openly gay father
Father so not much will be done until she commits mass murder. How can someone make a thread about?
Hey, can someone make a thread about blank? I won't say the name. There's a ton of info about her
I just said they don't have privileges to make new threads you can okay, so
She is on Twitter tweeting Trump
for help and having a meltdown threatening to mass murder everyone in porn that clowns on her.
She's also claiming everyone is jealous of her. Theoretically, a vigilante group could
take out easily every primary porn star pimp, agent, and their enablers, really just four
criminals pretending to be bloggers and three stupid lawyers, and L.E. wouldn't give a damn
or put much of any time into an investigation, just the theory. In times, I have a feeling
a few grand to one of the horse Kelly pimps to snap her neck. She deserves it. No one would care.
No one would investigate. No one even blog about it. Just another criminal out of circulation.
All you good old boys, don't get excited. I am not your little black girl bed wench. I am a solid
friend to the anti-porn activists and children and Christian Shelly Lou Ben who has opted to speak
and say a few things you could not state to enlighten her children. Do not fuck with me. Oh
Okay, she has made and then the video she looks highest buck. Okay, and then she teamed up with Melissa Hill
48 year old failed porn porn horror with a YouTube show called raw talk. She's met and then it's like, you know
Worst stuff I wanted I came and read some of the stuff because I'm not that mean of a person, okay?
I'm trying to keep it like very factual and not put not put their slanders in there, but man some of the things I've read, okay?
okay, and
She does want to help slay her enemies with the help of the Nazis in the KKK and would actually screaming about that ones
You see on the side that Christian has been tweeting on the court case. Yes, I guess there's a
Christian person she's in a short court case with
Okay
Okay, and so some of this stuff. I just can't say I'm just like I can't say right now
Because I'm too nice
Yeah, she was tweeting for yeah for help for the KKK. Yeah, well that was written down. But yeah
That's on it was on her it was on her older account. Yeah, I mean, I wish I could find I need to find those tweets
Let me see I just feel like she's a I
Mean this happened once before I mean a second so I could tell the cycle and everything also
She like speaking about I'm attracted to Brandon
I'm not sure, I'm not sure if she asked Brandon for sperm. She was certainly asking a lot of guys for guys for sperm
But I don't know. I don't think she would brand in but she did say he had a very very handsome face and he's good looking and
He's in his 30s. Well, I'm attracted to his young effeminate face
Who does he look like? I mean, he looks like rick moranis or something like that and he sounds like Burton Ernie
Um, I didn't find him
I I maybe I said I I said that in order to like fuck with people
Like Samann and Bita. I think I was on panel with them when I said just to fucking piss them off
But yeah, twack is funny
twack twack twack
So yeah, so in conclusion
This is about Brandon and
Alexandra this song applies or this uh, this applies to both of them and this will be on the way out. This is everybody
enjoy a little bit of Al Wilson and
Singing the snake. Thanks for being here everybody
long sat at the lake
A tender-hearted woman saw a poor half-frozen snake
His big-colored skin had been all frosted with a doom
Oh, well, she cried, I'll take you in and I'll take care of you
Take me in, oh tender woman
Take me in for heaven's sake
Take me in, tender woman
the snake. She ripped him up all cozy in a curvature of silk and then laid him by the
fireside with some honey and some milk. She ran home from work that night as soon as she arrived.
She found that pretty snake she had taken me in had been revived
Take me in, oh tender woman
Take me in for heaven's sake
Take me in, tender woman
This is the snake
She clutched him to a bosom
You're so beautiful that she cried
Now she's stooped
There's a pretty skin again
And then kissed
And held him tight
But instead of me and fake
A vicious fight
Woo!
Take me in
Oh, tin girl
Warm up and say
I'm the snake
The snake
One
Me and Eva
Take me in
Oh, tin girl
Warm up and say
I'm the snake
One more thing
You like that song, that is a great song, that is classic.
Yeah, so Brandon had, of course,
he's on the warpath right now.
He had posted some things,
and I just wanna go over a couple things he posted, hold on.
Well, first of all, you saw my kind of picture
of an alien with the mask,
and it was very, like, you don't know
what it was supposed to be of, but, right?
But he, at the same time I did that,
he decided to make one of his own,
of someone with a mask.
They're gone. His posts are gone. How do you do that? All his posts are gone. No, that's the wrong channel. Hold on.
I think it's the other channel.
Oh, yeah, here this one. So what does it say? It says posts. It says,
psyche, wait till you hear Karen call you a meth-head catabuser. And then
it says, I feel like an idiot. Psyche keeps disrespecting me 1037 Sunday. Okay, wait till I hear it.
I mean, it's like, you know what?
Maybe she's getting some some bad information. Hey, Brandon Q at cult of psyche at IRL news time. I beat his kitties
OMG, here's what I see. It's I can't really I mean, it's I don't even know he's posting this. Oh my gosh
I didn't know he keeps bringing up Alex. I shut that down though cuz watch he'll be buddies with all of them
You miss me fighting with maggot gamble the other night
He's a POS and I remember Daniel and said it he called me a bitch last week
He was kissing my ass because he wants everyone to believe a shit about you and a dog. It wasn't
It wasn't touched. So what was the video? I don't know. Well the video was you
You know scaring the shit out of some Mexican lady by banging on her door and ripping out the part apart her house
But if you want to see what he did about Alex, I'll show you the picture he did of Alex and
Here is the real Brandon and picturing. Here's how he's treating Alex and here's he's not even mad at him
But this is what the picture you made of Alex by the way, okay, do you see it? You see it, okay?
But I'm the bad I'm the bad guy, right? I said alien. She thinks she's an alien
She she's a pain. She's a picture painted of herself as half alien half black woman
So that was mine was almost kind of nice. This is just pure pure racism, right? You think she's a monkey, okay?
I never said anything like that. So what so what where's where's the uh, but she's not mad at brand
She's mad at me doesn't make any fucking sense, but hey, you know, you're dealing with
play witchy woman? Witchy woman. Well here's what I'm gonna play. I'm gonna play the Codex
Conspiracy because Codex Conspiracy is like last year um she thought like you know she or earlier
this year she said she thought my Codex was gonna be like used to blackmail and extort people and
all kinds of just bullshit right and she was saying that but then she came around to like
I made her the priestess of the cult and all kinds of things but like a dumbass but listen
She's been excommunicated, but let me just uh, I'll play you about the uh, the codex conspiracy
Ready to see it. Here you go
She logged in with the strong Wi-Fi lashes battle in the dawn said gather around my children put your little fear pants on
She had lore she had warnings. She had villains in a stack by the time she hit fraudulent psychic, baby
There was no turning back. She said he's got a codex and it's sinister obscene
Glitter-covered supervillain with a spreadsheet and a dream girl of codex is not Voldemort relax your sermon tone
You made a home
You say you're above the drama, yet you climb up on the floor You say you're not a character, then let that note
Stronger Wi-Fi, stronger lies, stronger monologue at night Every stream's a trial, every chat's a grand design
Stronger Wi-Fi, stronger size, stronger I'm too real for this, but you spawn a whole drag-offer I don't want imaginary diss
The sky a fog machine to kill a high government name government name
She sang it like a prayer like the social security office ought to hand her a tiara there
I'm not a character she cried while posing center stage baby even Shakespeare whisper
That's a lot of scene for one page. She said there's rumors that expect they'll see grid rings of doom
Like every time somebody types or even leave if someone cash apps lunch
She'll call the I've been quote the book of revel
Relation with the smoky narrowed eye. You say you don't need money. You say you don't need fame
Then why are you giving me a once full name stronger wife?
Stronger wife. Stronger wife. Scandal in the wing glare. Stronger wife. Stronger cry. Stronger Isle.
Listen psychic that trumpet to the sky. Girl, you stayed just season finale over one.
I the fraudulent psychic. The tech brain mystic. The codex cryptid. The king.
You said he runs the chatters and the donors and the
through the speech it sounded like you wanted top dollars joking now that line was looking tacky
but your response was so enormous it came dressed in sequence khaki you took a little
side comment and made it biblical in scope like jone crawford found a livestream and discovered christian
Cue the unstoppable soliloquy and fake retire
Cue the I don't need your friendship
Cue the I don't need your cash
Then 30 more dr-
Love exquisitely arranged trash
No dumb scream to now
As though she personal installed
The first command prompt on a cow
From bulletin boards to browsers from dial-
She walked in like St. Wikipedia with a kavel and perfume
Meanwhile all the girls in Gaze and Goblin's in the chat
We're watching this extravagance of thinking
Well, imagine that
A codex made her levitate
A psychic caused a quake in somehow every road
Let's back to look at before heaven takes
Stronger wi-fi, stronger lies
Stronger spotlight on your face
Every tale becomes
Imagine when you enter every space
Stronger Wi-Fi, stronger prize
Stronger, I'm the only truth
But your sermon wore a feather bow
And six wigs of you
Codex, listen, Codex, that ain't no cake on fire
You turned in each community
Spat into a Greek choir
Stronger Wi-Fi, stronger wise
Stronger need to testify
Saying I'm out of your show
I'll never
So here's to the stronger Wi-Fi, the louder
Decrease the grand girl reaction built for all to see she said I'm not a character with her hand
posed to the sky and the entire room in unison said baby there is a butterfly how hard it flies
Stronger wife I know in session would the psychic please
Yeah you said leave me alone
Then build a shrine out of screenshots, that's not distance, that's a season order.
You post another fake pic, another doom scroll spell
Tryna make me look crazy while you advertise yourself
Whole feet lookin' like a thish store, sense it with a ring like
Hello and a budget demonette, you don't care it's curses
You care it's content for the clouds, see my name all week
That's where you want me out, pulley lights in the window
Crossbows, huracurga, you storyboard my life, how do you own lor?
Lilith and her hashtags, I'm a yule in a tweet
Incher names, gettin' used to some rock n' bnb
That ain't mistake, that's panic with a filter and a font
That's how I need attention and a gothic redstone prime
You want dark, you want deep, you want fear to queen
But it's Canva
with a smoke machine talking like a puppet from another world gate hold
thanks for like a session with the side of hate
ring like Higgs, ring like Higgs, you keep building me a building
And just to form your checks, they don't contact me
Then it's post, post, post
You ain't haunted by a demon, you're haunted by ghosts
And they ghosts got my name in the center of your chest
I be faking for no means, just bulls of wrists
You don't want peace, you want content, stress
Ring light heads, ring light heads
You may need a sacrifice, my psycho, king too
That's a lot of fan fiction, just to say you're press boo
Messy room, green screen
Tablet on the table, levy in the screen
Please, believe I'm unstable, put the jokes on you
Cause the reeds too plain, you ain't exposing truth
You can raid in pain, borrow a single language
Dress it up in black when he in social week
Throw a demon on the tracks, said I'm above it
that leave me be while your manufacturer knows it's that online
I can be bitter turn loud trying to summon public shame from a copy past the cloud
You want myth, you want dread, you want queen or the damn
but it's grievance and extensions with a phone in your hand
Big bad priestess, off fire, no aim, whole ritual will collapse every time you say my name
Ring Light Hicks, Ring Light Hicks, you keep building me a villain just to farm your checks
They don't contact me, then it's post, post, post, you ain't haunted by demons
You're haunted by ghosts and they ghost got my name in the center of your chest
Every fake in front of me just proves a risk
You don't want peace, you want content and stress
Let's be honest
It's not revelation
It's a temper tantrum with reduction design you call it spiritual work or a spiraling art
You keep trying to burn my image cuz I'm stuck in your heart. That's not a cold power
That's a digital fit every post says more about you than it ever says
Hashtag witchcraft hashtag doom
Hashtag villain burning in the room
Hashtag prophet hashtag flames
Hashtag peace keeping erecting with my pain
Ring light hex, ring light hex
Every little's been campaign turned to self-effects
Say I'm the problems that you can't let go
You keep feeding me the spotlight from your little shadow
Show no ancient throne, no infant oppressed
Just recycled rage in a black lace dress
You don't want truth, you want content and stress
Ring light hex, ring light hex
So post another one
At far
that crows at thunder maybe next time in life outside of me too
so it's like the original original one i made is when she did the tommy james romance arc
she friended me with fireworks confetti in her hair said you're such a lovely soul with that
A temporary favorite in her very special use and look
She needed me for optics, for a sub block and for a scene
Poking at her right while pretending to be clean
I thought it was connection Turns out it was theater
A one-way auction call How can I eat her?
I was good enough for midnight talks
For spiral rants and victim analogies
But when the script got rewritten fast
She cut my name from every cast
She tells me with the curtains, dramatic drama
And then she floats into my panel like a ghost
And Mr. Don
That monster says I'm darkness doomed
I was a stain dried up until I got less useful
To a junior empire
That's rich coming from the patrons, ain't a change in every cast
She found a champion, knight in shining chrome
Boosted him like rescue merch, said finally I'm home
But the arm fairy day got haze
And even cessation said crazy
I stood there in the cheap seat
Watching plot twists hit the wall
Like me, that's your rich
Didn't he just miss your call?
Every week!
Every week a new Messiah
Every month a brand new scar
A rotating cast of light bulbs
That don't make it very false
There were some folks turned up to a courtroom filing
And I'll blame with a pageant smile
Contact me she whispers then appears where I live on air like boundaries off of peasants and hypocrisies
To the way now. I'm some spiritual trafficker. What's a deluxe invention?
There's not a charge. It's fanfiction with a persecution pension
She collects moral costumes and the state for the thumbnail pitch for for the rage the next day
Every friendship gets a trailer every fallout gets for her
I want popcorn because every grand denunciation comes pre-fraid and overworn
And if I'm such a beast, baby, why haunt my little show?
Why bang on the cathedral door? You swore you'd never contact me
Okay, cool her, then why are you memorizing every word?
Come die by me, then you keep orbiting my so-called monstrosity
I was useful